<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shima Dot Dev Blog</title>
    <link>https://shimadotdev.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shima Dot Dev Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://shimadotdev.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I Became a Superstar with a Telegram Bot!</title>
      <link>https://shimadotdev.github.io/posts/telegram-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://shimadotdev.github.io/posts/telegram-bot/</guid>
      <description>Usually, when we enter new work environments, it can be challenging to present ourselves in the right and suitable light, especially if our work experience or abilities are unclear to others, and this becomes even more difficult when you are a woman in the tech field!&#xA;About four years ago, I was introduced and invited to work at my current company through the recommendation of a former colleague (Hello Khani). It seemed that no woman had been hired there before, and as a developer, I was often perceived similarly to extraterrestrial beings D:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Lifestyle</title>
      <link>https://shimadotdev.github.io/posts/developer-lifestyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://shimadotdev.github.io/posts/developer-lifestyle/</guid>
      <description>Usually, until everything is in order and going well, we do not realize the importance of having a proper and healthy lifestyle. However, it is enough for a gradual increase in weight, joint problems, etc., to occur for us to remember that we need to make changes in our daily routine. In this article, I have specifically written about my experiences in life and work.&#xA;1. Exercise Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t have a weight problem, incorporating regular exercise (for example, three days a week) not only helps maintain a desirable weight but also reduces stress associated with work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Experience</title>
      <link>https://shimadotdev.github.io/posts/developer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://shimadotdev.github.io/posts/developer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Most likely, we are all familiar with the concept of UX or &amp;ldquo;User Experience,&amp;rdquo; or at least have heard its name. However, the term DX may be less common and less discussed. Developer Experience, or &amp;ldquo;Development Experience,&amp;rdquo; is used when our product is an API, and its audience is developers and programmers.&#xA;What is DX? DX is about the feelings of developers when interacting with an API. Since developers are generally considered intelligent individuals, this aspect may not receive much attention unless a company (with an API product) feels threatened by its competitors (with a similar product).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
