<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dockerfile on Shima Dot Dev Blog</title>
    <link>https://shimadotdev.github.io/tags/dockerfile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dockerfile on Shima Dot Dev Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://shimadotdev.github.io/tags/dockerfile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Docker Guide for Beginners: Dockerfile, Image and Container</title>
      <link>https://shimadotdev.github.io/posts/docker-image-container/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://shimadotdev.github.io/posts/docker-image-container/</guid>
      <description>Docker Installation Before anything else, it is necessary to install Docker on your system. For installation on Mac, Windows, and Ubuntu, you can use Docker&amp;rsquo;s official guide.&#xA;Building an Image Let&amp;rsquo;s start by creating our first image in the simplest way possible:&#xA;First, create a directory in the terminal using the command mkdir myfirst.&#xA;In the next step, create a Dockerfile with touch Dockerfile.&#xA;Enter the following commands into the Dockerfile:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Guide for Beginners: Keywords in Docker</title>
      <link>https://shimadotdev.github.io/posts/docker-keywords/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://shimadotdev.github.io/posts/docker-keywords/</guid>
      <description>Docker Engine The Docker Engine is the layer on which Docker runs, and its task is to manage containers, images, building, etc. This layer sits right above the host machine&amp;rsquo;s operating system and performs its tasks by receiving commands from the client (for example, the terminal).&#xA;Dockerfile A Dockerfile is where the necessary instructions for building an image are written. If you take a look at existing Dockerfiles, you will see sample commands like RUN apt-get install something; these commands allow us to install necessary packages for running software in an isolated container environment, assign ports, or define directories.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
